brokengold.com 2014-04-26

# BrokenGold.com Privacy Policy - Sell Scrap Gold & Broken Jewelry Online

**Broken Gold is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.**

TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the websites [www.brokengold.com](http://www.brokengold.com/) , and www.sellgold.com. From this point on the above listed websites will be referred to as “The Sites” or “We, Us, Our”. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Tevin Jones at the phone number **1-888-920-5111**. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php/). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

* * *

**The following applies only to North Carolina residents.**  
Brokengold.com may, from time to time, share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As a North Carolina resident, you have a legal right to request and receive in writing or by email the names and addresses of all such third parties who received your personally identifiable information during the previous calendar year and a list of the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to such third parties. To request such information, send an email to support@brokengold.com or write to North Carolina Privacy Information c/o Brokengold.com, 2437 N Church St Burlington NC 27217. We will not honor such request more than once per calendar year.  
For more information on how your personally identifiable information is collected and used, please read our Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Policy  
Effective as of May 11, 2009**

Brokengold.com ("we," "us," "our") makes this Web site (the "Site") available to consumers who are interested in obtaining information regarding obtaining cash for broken or unwanted jewelry ("Consumers"), subject to this privacy policy (the "Policy") and the Site's terms and conditions of use ("Terms and Conditions"). This Policy explains what information we collect on the Site, how we use and/or share this information, and how such information is maintained. By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, in whole or part, you should not use this Site.

Note that this Policy applies only with respect to the information collected on the Site and not any information collected or obtained through other methods or sources.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
**Collection of PII**

We collect personally identifiable information ("PII") that is volunteered during the registration process or in response to specific information requests explicitly presented to Consumers. To use our product you will be requested to provide the following PII: first and last name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

**Use and Sharing of PII**

We reserve the right to use PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided (to enable our third party partners (the "Jewelry Purchaser") to provide you with the opportunity to exchange your broken or unwanted jewelry for payment, (2) as disclosed at the time such information is provided; and/or (3) as disclosed in this Policy. However, please note that we may change this Policy at any time (See "Changes to this Policy," below), and that therefore we may in the future use PII for additional purposes not currently included in this Policy.

As provided in the Terms and Conditions, users of the Site are required to provide their PII to us so that we may use such information to enable the Jewelry Purchaser to provide you with information regarding exchanging your broken or unwanted jewelry and/or other broken or unwanted gold pieces, and to understand and agree that we may share their PII with unaffiliated third parties, including the Jewelry Purchaser. If you do not provide the required PII or do not agree that we may share your PII with such entities, as set forth in this Policy, you will not be provided with information regarding jewelry purchase and should not use this site.

Additionally, we may share with/transfer to third-parties PII in aggregate, non-personal form, for purposes of commercial email marketing, telemarketing, and all other forms of online marketing including, but not limited to, pop-ups, pop-unders, redirects, and/or online banner advertising and SMS text based marketing.

Finally, we may disclose PII in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; and (4) protect our rights or property, this Site, and/or other users of this Site.

By registering and using this Site, Members acknowledge that the processing of their PII for the purposes described above may involve the transfer of such PII from within the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union.

**Anti-Spyware Policy**

Brokengold.com believes that Spyware is a threat to consumer privacy and a consumer's experience online. Therefore, we forbid any Brokengold.com employee, agent, partner, affiliate or contractor from intentionally deploying or using Spyware (as defined in this policy) on behalf of Brokengold.com. Spyware refers to any executable software application that is installed on a user's personal computer and covertly gathers and transmits PII through the user's Internet connection without the knowledge or consent of the user. Cookies and web beacons are not considered Spyware. Spyware may gather PII, such as e-mail addresses and credit card information, and may even alter personal computer settings. Intentional use of Spyware by any Brokengold.com employee, agent, partner or affiliate on Brokengold.com's behalf will not be tolerated and will be considered grounds for dismissal, contract termination and/or loss of payment.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information through the standard operation of our servers. Such information can include the non-personally identifiable information more fully described below.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" on the Site. Cookies are small pieces of information that our server places on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site.

While some Web browsers allow a user to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the user's computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that cookies provide.

**IP Address**

We collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer this Site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.

**Clear GIFs**

We use a common technology known as a "Clear GIF" or "1-by-1 Pixel" on the Site and in e-mail communications with users. A Clear GIF, or "graphic interface format" is a small graphic (in fact, truly a 1x1 pixel) that we (or our partners) place on a page of the Site. We may also occasionally place GIFs in e-mail messages that we send to users. GIFs, which do not contain any PII, provide us with important information about how users use the Site and respond to e-mail messages. With this information, we are better able to track the performance of certain promotions and understand the effectiveness of particular creative e-mail presentations. We may also allow our advertisers and promotional partners the ability to use GIFs on the Site solely to track users who link from their respective sites to this Site, but this ability to track such activity does not allow these entities access to user PII.

Although the information collected through the foregoing methods does not itself contain any PII, we may analyze and match such information with other information that you provide on this Site (including PII) as well as information that we may obtain elsewhere, and we may share all or some of such information with partners, prospective partners, and other affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. We may also disclose non-personally identifiable information in order to (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, or (4) protect our rights or property, this Site and/or users of this Site.

**Agents**

Brokengold.com may employ other companies and individuals to perform services on its behalf and on behalf of the Network Sites, such as (1) administering sweepstakes, contests and other promotions, (2) sending emails, (3) providing marketing assistance, and (4) database management and analysis. Such companies and individuals will have access to Member PII only to the extent necessary to perform their services, but will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose.

**Linking of Information**

We may combine information provided by a user with information obtained from other sources. Enhancing user files with this other information will allow us to provide users with more relevant services and offers. Likewise, any information entered by a user on this Site could be used to update that user's profile on third party sites.

**Opt-Out of Our E-mail Promotions**

When you sign up on the Site, you will automatically be registered to receive promotional offers and site updates, via e-mails, from us. Additionally, when you sign up, you will be provided with the opportunity to receive promotional offers, via e-mail, from our third party partners (including the "Jewelry Purchaser").

Users may, at any time, choose not to receive promotional e-mails from us, or our partners by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in our e-mail. We will respond to a request to "unsubscribe" as promptly as possible. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may at any time contact users for the purpose of communicating important information about us or the Site.

**Third Party Services**

The information regarding unwanted or broken jewelry and/or other unwanted or Broken Gold™ pieces will be provided by the Jewelry Purchaser. Although we advise all of our partners to support this Policy, we have no control over their information handling practices and are not responsible for any failure of such partners (or unaffiliated third parties) to adhere to this Policy.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, if any, third-party advertisers or ad servers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such third party advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies.

**Links from the Site**

This Site provides links to many of our advertiser and partner Web sites or other Web sites. If you link to any of these third party Web sites, this Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including their privacy policies. We shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites.

**Note Concerning Visitors Under 18 Years of Age**

Use of the Site, is neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 18.

**Security**

While we take reasonable precautions to safeguard information transmitted between the Site and and/or users, we may be unable to prevent unauthorized access to such information by third parties or inadvertent disclosure of such information. Users acknowledge this risk when communicating with the Site.

**Consent to Processing**

By providing PII and other information to this Site, users fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in, and the transfer of such information to, the United States and other countries or territories, in accordance with the terms of this Policy.

**Transfer in Certain Circumstances**

In our sole discretion, we may transfer, sell or assign information collected on and through this Site, including without limitation, PII and other information, to one or more third parties, as a result of our sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation.

**Customer Service**

If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to contact us at: Brokengold.com; Attn. Customer Service; 2437 N Church St Burlington NC 27217 or via email at support@brokengold.com.

**Changes to this Policy**

We may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in our sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy on the Site. Depending on the nature of the change, we may announce the change (1) on the home page of the Site, or (2) provide such notice via e-mail to users. By continuing to use the Site following any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, you must terminate your site usage.

**California Residents Privacy Rights:**  
Companies that collect personally identifiable information ("PII") from California residents and disclose such information to Third Parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with Third Parties. We have elected the second option and you may request that your PII not be shared with Third Parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to: BrokenGold.com Unsubscribe 2533 N. Carson St., Suite 3927 Carson City, NV 89706. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov. If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at info@BrokenGold.com

 **Detailed Wireless Policy**

Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. We may share aggregated and non personal information with third parties outside of www.brokengold.com When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to support@brokengold.com or by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. 

Presented by:  
Brokengold.com  
2437 N Church St   
Burlington NC 27217

©2008 BGC MANAGEMENT, INC. - Sell Gold, Scrap Silver, Old Jewelry & More at BrokenGold.com
